(Sheldon:)That was a joke.
(Sheldon:)It's funny because it's true.
(Sheldon:)Leonard,
could you pass the soy sauce, please?
- I'm sorry, were you talking to me?
- Yeah, I said Leonard.
(Leonard:)Yes, you did, didn't you?
(Penny:)What the hell is that?
(Howard:)Meatloaf.
(Leonard:)What was it doing on the ceiling?
(Howard:)That's classified.
ASTRONAUT [OVER RADIO]:
Houston, Internationale Space Station.
(Voice:)We have a little situation up here.
(Voice:)We'd like to make an unscheduled
space walk.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
ISS, Houston...
(Houston:)...which crew members
would be involved in this EVA?
ASTRONAUT: Houston, we'd all like
to step outside for a few minutes.
MAN:
ISS, I'm afraid we can't authorize that.
ASTRONAUT:
Houston, this is more of an FYI call.
(ISS voice:)We are basically out the door.